		Systems Verification and Monitoring

Panel 13:
	1 Mount ORDEAL BOX 
		This is automatically mounted as a panel in Reentry.

	2 Perform Propulsion System: C&WS Oper Check

	3 Perform Propulsion System: SM RCS Mon Check

	4 Perform Propulsion System: CM RCS Mon Check

	5 Perform EPS Checks:
		Cryo PSI-Qty check
		FC Power Plant check
		D-C Voltage-Amperage check
		A-C Voltage check

	6 Perform ECS Mon Check

	7 Perform SPS Mon Check

Panel 226:
	8 cb FC REACS (3) - open (verify)
		cb COAS/TUNL LTG MNB - close
