


		RCS/SPS ABORT MODES II, III, IV
		
Mode  II, III, and IV aborts are manually initiated and utilize the SM RCS to provide a safe separation distance from the SIVB. After separation and CSM stabilization, the abort possibilities separate into three categories.

		 • CM/SM separation and coast-to-landing site (MODE II).	
		 • Shaped trajectory abort utilizing an SPS variable
		    maneuver to correct the trajectory for the desired landing
			site in the Atlantic Recovery Area (MODE III).
		 • Abort-to-earth-orbit utilizing the SPS to attain earth 
			orbital altitude and speed (MODE IV).
