		SPS Monitoring Check

Panel 3:
	SPS PRPLNT TEMP ind - +45° to +75°
		If <45°F, SPS LINE HTRS - A
		If >75°F, SPS LINE HTRS - off (ctr)
	SPS PRESS IND sw - He, N2A, & N2B
		SPS He/N2 PRESS ind
			SPS He PRESS - 3900 psia max
			SPS N2 A PRESS - 2900 psia max
			SPA N2 B PRESS - 2900 psia max
	SPS PRESS IND sw - He
	SPS FUEL PRESS ind - 170-195 psia
	SPS OXID PRESS ind - 170-195 psia


			CAUTION

		If ∆P between fuel & oxid is
		>20 psi prior to critical SPS
		burn, repressurize prplnt tks
		manually by placing SPS He VLV
		(both) - ON. ∆P between tks
		>20 psi during a burn may result
		in degraded performance, rough
		combustion, &/or eng failure.
		Refer to SPS malfunction symptom.

Panel 3:
	SPS INJ VLV ind (4) - CLOSE

	SPS OXID QTY ind - record
	SPS FUEL QTY ind - record
	SPS OXID UNBAL ind - record
	OXID FLOW VLV PRIM - PRIM

	

			CAUTION

		Do not sw to sec oxid flow vlv
		with prim vlv functioning properly.
		Failure of sec vlv could result in
		loss of prplnt management capabil-
		ity. If OXID FLOW VLV PRIM sw
		inadvertently set to SEC when no
		failure exists, return to PRIM
		before repositioning OXID FLOW VLV
		INCR sw.

	SPS He VLV (both) - AUTO
	SPS He VLV tb (both) - bp
