		PROPULSION SYSTEMS

Specific functions of the SPS and RCS must be monitored to assure operational readiness and capability. SPS and SM RCS monitoring checks are performed during post-orbital insertion check and at 4-hour intervals and after each SPS burn. 

In addition, the SM RCS monitoring check is performed prior to each SPS burn. The CM RCS monitoring check is performed during post-orbital insertion check and at 12-hour intervals and prior to entry.
