This is a helper checklist and contains the RUN feature to align the IMU to the preferred orientation, suggested by the CSM burn tool and P30/P40.

It will align the IMU to the burn direction, so at the time of ignition, pitch and yaw will be zero. This attitude should be held and maintained throughout the burn.

Refer to the P52 checklist as you use the RUN feature here.

When running P52, you will enter code +00001 (preferred option), then accept the attitude. The gyros will be aligned with the new reference orientation.
