This is a helper checklist, and contains the RUN feature to perform the IMU realignment of the REFSMMAT using P52, option 3.

You will still use the (P52) IMU REALIGN checklist, but the RUN feature of this checklist to guide you through the correct path of the complex checklist.

When running P52, you will enter code +00003 (REFSMMAT option).
Then you will MARK two sightings.

To enter the SCT or the SXT, press the respective scope. You can change in scope view too using the small arrow next to the current scope title.

V51 means that the AGC is waiting for a mark. Enter the scope, use CTRL+Arrow keys to move the scope. Center a target in the SXT (use SCT for searching, then SXT to perform the mark) and press MARK.

You can choose the mark yourself, even if the AGC/N70 shows another star ID. If the star you marks differ from the suggested ID, simply change N71 when it shows to the correct star with V21E+000XX where XX is the star ID.

When two marks are complete, the difference will show. This is the angular difference between your marks and the known angular difference between the two marks. This should be less than 0.03 degrees (00003). If above, redo the procedure.
