This is a helper checklist to perform SPS burns such as LOI using the SPS burn maneuver planner.

1.
	In the CSM Burn Planner create a manuver with a
	dV of ~3150 ft/s and a Phase of 0 in the Retrograde direction.

		Note: This is for LOI. Play with the values until you get 
		desired target Ap/Pe.

	Panel 8
		RCS LOGIC MNA & MNB Closed.

	Panel 2
		SM RCS Helium and PRPLNT Open.

2.
	V37E 30E
		F V06 N33
	PRO
		F V06 N81
	PRO
		F V06 N42
	PRO
		F V16 N45
		Set event timer to 20m00s and ensure its set to countdown.
		R2 is T- to burn. Wait until T- ~20m.
	Start Event Timer.
	PRO
		Verify that Panel 13: FDAI 1 & 2 are set to INRTL.
	CAUTION: If either is set to ORB RATE P40 will not work properly
 

3.
	Run P52 Opt 1. (or run the P52 Aid: preferred checklist) then come 	       back and do item 4.

4.
	V37E 40E
	PRO
		F V06 N18
		Use V21E, V22E and V23E to set R1, 2 and 3 to +00000.
	PRO
		F V50 N18
	PRO
		F V50 N25

5.
	Set CMC MODE to AUTO
	and if needed use manual translation to aid speeding up the att change.
	Ensure ATT is 0,0,0

	Arm the SPS THRUST Switches.

6.
	PRO
		F V06 N40
			R1 reads T- to burn in seconds
		T- 5s 
			F V99
		PRO
	Wait until the burn is compleate, and be ready to press 
	PRO if something goes wrong.

	Once the burn is compleate press PRO until the DKSY reads P00.

7. 
	Disarm SPS THRUST.
