GYRO ALIGN

Use ONLY if errors in GYRO

1. Gyro 				- GYRO CAGE
2. Attitude			- 0, 0, 0
Maneuver the attitude to the 0,0,0 attitude, using window reference, eye sight, or periscope.
3. Gyro 				- NORMAL or FREE

HORIZON CHECK

1. Attitude			- RETROGRADE
Align the spacecraft with the retrograde horizon. You can also use the marks on the periscope
The readings should read about 0, 0, 0
If not, realign the gyros
