LANDING

DROGUE CHUTE FAILURE
Drogue chute failure can be detected by the lack of opening shock and by a visual check through the window. Failure of the Emer Drogue Deploy fuse will fail the Drogue Override button.

1. Drogue button - DEPRESS
2. If drogue chute does not deploy:
	a. Emer Drogue Deploy fuse switch - NO. 2
	b. Drogue button - DEPRESS


MAIN CHUTE FAILURE
Main chute deployment failure can be detected by the lack of opening shock, a visual check through the periscope and window, and no decrease in rate of descent.

If the main chute does not deploy properly or is damaged:
1. Reserve deploy ring - PULL


LANDING BAG FAILS TO DEPLOY
1. Landing Bag switch - MAIN
2. Emer Land Bag fuse switch - NO. 2
