Test CL!

FLY-BY-WIRE MODE

1. ASCS switch 			- FLY-BY-WIRE
2. RSCS switch 			- AUTO
3. Manual Fuel Handle 	- PUSH RATE COMD
4. Use handcontroller to desired attitude

COMPLETE INTERIOR INSPECTION (T-90)

ELECTRICAL POWER SYSTEM
Note: These switches are located on both sides of the crew seat.
1. Main Battery No. 1 - IN (ON)
2. Main Battery No. 2 - ON
3. Main Battery No. 3 - IN (ON)
4. Stby Battery No. 1 - IN (ON)
5. Stby Battery No. 2 - IN (ON)
6. Isol Battery - IN (ON)

COMPLETE INTERIOR INSPECTION
1. All switch fuses 			- NO. 1 POSITION
2. Squib switch 				- OFF
3. Auto retro jett switch 	- ARM
4. ASCS mode select switches - 
	a. ASCS switch 			- NORM
	b. RSCS switch 			- AUTO
	c. Gyro switch 			- GYRO NORM
5. Control fuel handles 	- IN
	a. Manual fuel handle 	- PUSH RATE COMD
	b. Roll fuel handle 	- PUSH ON
	c. Yaw fuel handle 		- PUSH ON
	d. Pitch fuel handle 	- PUSH ON
6. Retro delay switch 		- INST
7. Photo lights switch 		- ON
8. Cabin lights switch 		- BOTH
9. TLM-LO freq switch 		- ON
10. Rescue switch 			- AUTO
11. Launch Contl switch 	- OFF
12. Jett Tower Ring 			- IN
13. Sep Capsule Ring 		- IN
14. Retro Att switch 		- AUTO
15. Fire Retro Push Button 	- GUARD INSTALLED
16. Jett Retro Push Button	- GUARD INSTALLED
17. Retract Scope switch		- AUTO
18. Snorkel Ring 			- IN
19. Main Ring 				- IN
20. Reserve Ring 			- IN
21. Landing Bag switch 		- AUTO
22. Control Fuel Qty gauges	- CHECK
      a. Auto Fuel 			- 100%
      b. Manual Fuel 		- 100%
23. Rate of Descent 			- 0 FT/SEC
24. Altimeter 				- CHECK
25. Satellite clock
      a. Time of Day
      b. Time from launch 	- ZERO
      c. Time to Retrograde
26. Attitude/Rate ind. 		- CHECK
      a. Rate indicators 	- CENTER
      b. Attitude indicators - CHECK
27. Time Zero Cover 			- REMOVE
28. Cabin pressure 			- CHECK
29. Cabin Air temp 			- CHECK
30. Suit Env. Indicator 		- CHECK
31. Oxygen Quantity 		- CHECK
      a. Primary 			- 100%
      b. Secondary 			- 100%
32. Suit Fan switch 		- NORM
33. Cabin Fan switch 		- NORM
34. DC Volts knob 			- MAIN
35. Ammeter switch			- PWR OFF
36. ASCS AC Bus 			- NORM
37. Stby Btry switch 		- ON
38. Isol Btry switch 		- STBY
39. Inlet Valve Pwr switch 	- NORM
40. Audio Bus switch 		- NORM
41. AC voltmeter				- 115 VOLTS (109v-121v)
42. VOX Pwr switch 			- OFF
43. UHF DF switch 			- NORM
44. UHF select switch 		- HI PWR
45. Transmit switch 			- OFF
46. Beacon switch 			- GRND COMD
47. All Audio Tone switches - ON
48. Warning Lights switch 	- BRIGHT
49. Emer O2 switch 			- NORM
50. Suit Temp selector 		- TO MARK
51. Cabin Temp selector 		- TO MARK
52. Inverter Temp selector 	- TO MARK
53. Maneuver - ON
	This spins up the gyros. Please allow 5 minutes spin-up time.

At T-40:
	Start ABORT CAPABILITY Checklist

MANUAL MODE

1. Manual fuel handle 		- PULL DIRECT
2. ASCS switch 				- AUX ON
3a. If aux damping is desired, 
	RSCS switch 			- AUTO
3b. If aux damping is not desired,
	RSCS switch 			- RATE COMD

RATE COMMAND MODE

1. Manual fuel handle 		- PUSH RATE COMD
2. RSCS switch 				- RATE COMD
3. Use handcontroller to maintain desired rates and attitude

NORMAL MODE

1. ASCS switch 			- NORM
2. RSCS switch 			- AUTO
3. Manual Fuel Handle 	- PUSH RATE COMD

ABORT CAPABILITY (T-40)

1. Ammeter Switch 			- NORM
2. Capsule Squib Switch 	- ARM
3. DC Selector 				- ISOL.
4. REQUEST ABORT CAPABILITY TEST
5. Monitor bus voltage, battery current and Abort light.

At T-20:
	Start ABBR. INTERIOR CHECK

ABBREVIATED INTERIOR CHECK (T-20)

1. All left panel fuses 		- NO. 1 POSITION
2. Squib switch 				- ARM
3. Auto retro jett switch 	- ARM
4. ASCS Mode Select switch	- NORM
5. RSCS Mode Select switch 	- AUTO
6. Retro delay switch 		- NORM
7. Rescue switch 			- AUTO
8. Press Reg Handle 		- IN
9. Retro Att switch 			- AUTO
10. Retract Scope switch 	- AUTO
11. Landing Bag switch 		- AUTO
12. Control Fuel
      a. Auto Fuel: ___
      b. Manual Fuel: ___
13. Cabin Pressure Indicator: ___
14. Cabin Temp Indicator: ___
15. Suit Temp Indicator: ___
16. Suit Press Indicator: ___
17. Primary Oxygen: ___
18. Secondary Oxygen: ___
19. Suit Fan switch 		- NORM
20. Cabin Fan switch 		- NORM
21. DC Volts knob 			- MAIN
22. Ammeter switch 			- NORM
23. ASCS AC Bus Switch 		- NORM
24. Stby Btry switch 		- ON
25. Isol Btry switch 		- STBY
26. Inlet Valve Pwr switch 	- NORM
27. Audio Bus switch 		- NORM
28. Fans AC Bus switch 		- NORM
29. VOX Pwr switch 			- OFF
30. UHF DF switch 			- NORM
31. UHF Select switch 		- HI PWR
32. Transmit switch 			- OFF
33. Beacon switch 			- CONT
34. Emer O2 handle 			- NORM

At T-10:
	Start FULL INTERNAL POWER Checklist

SWITCH TO FULL INTERNAL POWER (T-10)

1. Monitor capsule battery voltage and current while the Blockhouse 
	switches to external power.
2. Request Blockhouse to remove external power
	Use the Tools Menu (default mapping: [C]) below radio panel
3. Isol Btry switch 			- NORM
4. Stby Btry switch 		- OFF

Start FINAL CHECKS

FINAL CHECKS
(Approx. T-5 to T-0)

1. Launch Control switch 		- READY
2. Suit Temp 					- TO MARK
3. Cabin Temp 					- TO MARK
4. Inverter Temp 				- TO MARK
5. Transmit 						- UHF
6. Perform Radio Check on UHF
7. Verify Time Zero Button 		- COVER REMOVED
	WARNING: Do not depress the time zero button
8. DC Volts knob 				- 1
9. Squib switch					- ARM
10. Auto Retro Jett switch		- ARM

At T-30 Seconds:
	Start ASCENT Checklist

GYRO ALIGN

Use ONLY if errors in GYRO

1. Gyro 				- GYRO CAGE
2. Attitude			- 0, 0, 0
Maneuver the attitude to the 0,0,0 attitude, using window reference, eye sight, or periscope.
3. Gyro 				- NORMAL or FREE

HORIZON CHECK

1. Attitude			- RETROGRADE
Align the spacecraft with the retrograde horizon. You can also use the marks on the periscope
The readings should read about 0, 0, 0
If not, realign the gyros

ASCENT

1. Monitor Abort Light
2. Monitor Isolated Battery Voltage
3. Monitor Cabin Pressure
    a. Will go from 15 to 5.5
4. Monitor DC Voltage
5. Monitor DC Ammeter
6. Monitor AC Voltage

At Engine Cutoff:
	If Redstone Rocket Launch:
		Start REDSTONE Ascent Checklist
	If Atlas Rocket Launch:
		Start BECO Checklist

PRE-DARK

1. Cabin Light switch 			- BOTH
2. Photo Lights 				- OFF
3. Red filters on cabin light 	- [Click on the lights]
4. Red scope filter 				- ON
5. Warning lights 				- DIM
6. Thruster warmup procedure:
 (a) Enable MANUAL flight mode:
      Pitch UP followed by pitch DOWN
      Roll RIGHT followed by roll LEFT
      Yaw RIGHT followed by yaw LEFT

 (b) Enable FLY-BY-WIRE flight mode:
      Short-burst pitch UP and DOWN - full stick travel
      Short-burst roll RIGHT and LEFT - full stick travel
      Short-burst yaw RIGHT and LEFT - full stick travel

 (c) ASCS mode and check for proper attitude orientation and holding 
	within limits

7. After entry into dark side, filters - as desired

ASCENT/REDSTONE

1. Jett Tower 					- GREEN (appx. T+2:10 and 20 sec after 
									MECO)
2. Sep Capsule					- GREEN (appx. 15 sec after Tower Jett)
3. Auto Retro Jett switch 		- OFF
4. Retro Jett Fuse switch 		- OFF
5. Emer Retro Jett Fuse switch 	- OFF

Start ORBIT Checklist

PRE-DAY

1. Cabin Light switch 			- BOTH
2. Photo Lights 				- ON
3. White filters on cabin light 	- [Click on the lights]
4. Red scope filter 				- OFF
5. Warning lights 				- BRIGHT
6. Thruster warmup procedure:
 (a) Enable MANUAL flight mode:
      Pitch UP followed by pitch DOWN
      Roll RIGHT followed by roll LEFT
      Yaw RIGHT followed by yaw LEFT

 (b) Enable FLY-BY-WIRE flight mode:
      Short-burst pitch UP and DOWN - full stick travel
      Short-burst roll RIGHT and LEFT - full stick travel
      Short-burst yaw RIGHT and LEFT - full stick travel

 (c) ASCS mode and check for proper attitude orientation and holding 
	within limits

7. After entry into dark side, filters - as desired

ASCENT/BECO

1. Jett Tower					- AMBER
2. Jett Tower 					- GREEN (appx. 20 sec after BECO)
3. Auto Retro Jett switch 		- OFF
4. Retro Jett Fuse switch 		- OFF
5. Emer Retro Jett Fuse switch 	- OFF

Start SECO Checklist

ASCENT/SECO

At SECO:
1. Sep Cap 	- AMBER, then GREEN

Start ORBIT Checklist

PRE RETRO (Tr-30)

Approximately 30 minutes before retro time (Tr-30mins):
1. Cabin Temp 			- COLD
2. Suit Temp 			- COLD
3. Inverter Temp 		- COLD

Approximately 15 minutes before retro time (Tr-15mins):
4. Emer Retro Seq. Fuse 		- ON
5. 1, 2, 3 Retro Rckt Fuse 	- ON
6. Emer Retro Jet Fuse 		- ON
7. ASCS .05G Fuse 			- ON
8. Emer .05G Fuse 			- ON
9. Periscope Fuse 			- ON
10. Cmd Rcvr A Fuse 		- ON
11. TLM Hi Freq Fuse 		- ON
12. Squib switch 			- ARM
13. Auto Retro Jett switch 	- OFF
14. TLM Lo Freq switch 		- ON
15. Transmit switch 			- UHF
16. BCN switch 				- CONT
17. Retro Jett Fuse 			- OFF
18. Retro Man Fuse 			- ON
19. Attitude Select 			- RETRO
20. Maintain Retro attitude

Start RETRO Checklist

RETRO

At Tr -5 Mins:
"5 Min To Retrograde" light 	- ILLUMINATED

At Tr +0 Secs:
1. "Retro Seq" telelight 		- GREEN
2. "Retro Att" telelight 		- GREEN

At Tr +20 Secs:
1. "Retro Warn" telelight 		- AMBER & Audible Tone
4. Crosscheck attitude indicator, periscope and window
5. "Fire Retro" telelight 		- AMBER while firing
6. "Fire Retro" telelight 		- GREEN once completed

Start RE-ENTRY Checklist

RE-ENTRY

1. Fire Retro Green:
    a. Auto Retro switch 		- ARM
    b. Retro Jett Fuse 			- ON
    c. Emer Retro Jett Fuse 	- ON
2. Jett Retro Telelight goes green 60 seconds after Retro Fire signal.
3. Attitude Select 				- RE-ENT
4. Check correct attitude
5. Monitor attitude indicator until .05G
6. .05G Telelight 				- GREEN
7. Rate indicator shows 10*/SEC roll rate

After Re-entry:
	Start LANDING CHECKLIST

ORBIT

1. DC Volts knob 			- MAIN
2. Landing Bag switch 		- OFF
3. Retro Delay switch 		- NORM
4. Emer Retro Seq Fuse 		- OFF
5. Emer Drogue Deploy Fuse - OFF
6. All instruments 			- CHECK

If out-of-range from radio station, set UHF PWR - HI for longer reach

LANDING

1. Emer Drogue Fuse 				- ON (BEFORE 30,000 FT)
2. At 21,000 ft. check drogue chute deployment
3. At appx. 20,000ft, Snorkel Ring 	- PULL
4. Emer O2 handle 					- EMER
5. Landing Bag switch 				- AUTO
6. At 10,000 ft, "Main" light 		- GREEN 
7. UHF/DF switch 					- R/T
8. Press Reg Handle 				- PULL
9. "Landing Bag" Telelight 			- GREEN

After Impact:
1. ASCS AC Bus switch 				- OFF
2. Photo Lights switch 				- OFF

LAUNCH AND ASCENT

ABORT

		WARNING
If ISOL. BUS is lost, an abort is not possible.

Abort Prior to Tower Jettison
1. Abort handle					- CTRL+SHIFT+Z
2. "Sep Capsule" telelight		- GREEN
3. "Jett Tower"					- GREEN
4. "Jett Retro" 					- GREEN
5. Check that the ASCS positions the capsule in retrograde attitude. Use manual control if needed.
	a. ATTITUDE SELECT			- RETRO
	b. RETRO ATT 				- AUTO
	c. SQUIB						- ARM
	d. AUTO RETRO JETT			- ARM
6. Monitor altimeter and complete normal landing procedures with manual override if needed.

Start LANDING Checklist

Abort After Tower Jettison
1. Abort handle					- CTRL+SHIFT+Z
2. "Sep Capsule" telelight		- GREEN
3. Check that the ASCS positions the capsule in retrograde attitude. Use manual control if needed.
	a. ATTITUDE SELECT			- RETRO
	b. RETRO ATT 				- AUTO
	c. SQUIB						- ARM
	d. AUTO RETRO JETT			- ARM
4. Fire the retrograde rockets when in retro attitude and ready.
5. Monitor altimeter and complete normal landing procedures with manual override if needed.

Start LANDING Checklist


TOWER FAILS TO JETTISON
1. Jett Tower ring 							- ACTUATE
2. If tower fails to jettison:
	a. Emer Twr Sep fuse switch 			- NO. 2
	b. For normal jettison, 
		Emer Escape Rkt fuse switch 		- NO. 2.
	c. On aborts, 
		Emer Twr Jett fuse switch 			- NO. 2.
3. If escape rocket still does not fire, 
		Abort handle						- CTRL+SHIFT+Z

CAPSULE FAILS TO SEPARATE FROM BOOSTER
1. Sep Capsule ring 					- PULL
2. If capsule fails to separate on abort before staging,
	Emer Escape Rkt fuse switch 	- NO. 2

ORBIT

ABORT FROM ORBIT
1. In the event an emergency requiring an immediate abort:
	a. Emer Retro Seq Fuse Switch 			- ON
	b. Retro Seq Button 					- DEPRESS
		or Fire the retros manually

2. If conditions permit:
	a. Select recovery area.
	b. Compute retrograde time.
	c. If time permits, reset retrograde clock.
	d. If there is insufficient time, 30 seconds before
 retrograde time, 
		Retro Seq button 					- DEPRESS
			or Fire the retros manually

3. Start PRE-RETRO Checklist

STABILIZATION SYSTEM EMERGENCY OPERATION

Failure of Automatic Mode
If the automatic mode fails and the capsule is tumbling,
 switch to Rate Command to stop the tumbling and use
 manual control to return the capsule to desired attitude

1. Use rate command to stop any tumbling.
	a. Manual fuel handle 		- PUSH RATE COMD
	b. RSCS switch 				- RATE COMD
	c. Stop tumbling
	d. Reposition capsule to orbit attitude

2. Switch to manual mode.
	a. Manual fuel handle 		- PULL DIRECT
	b. ASCS switch 				- AUX DAMP
	c. If ASCS damping is desired, 
		RSCS switch 			- AUTO

3. Auto control fuel gauge 		- CHECK

Failure of Fly-By-Wire
Failure of fly-by-wire may occur in conjunction with failure
 of the automatic mode. If it occurs without failure of the
 automatic mode, there is probably an electrical malfunction
 in the control system fly-by-wire switches, ASCS switch, or
 associated circuits. Return to automatic mode, unless it
 has also failed, or switch to manual mode.

1. Auto control fuel gauge 			- CHECK
2. ASCS switch 						- NORM
3. If the automatic mode also has failed,
	manual control fuel handle 	- PULL DIRECT
4. Manually maintain proper attitude

Failure of Rate Command
If rate command fails in orbit, switch to manual or fly-by-wire
 mode if manual control is desired, or to automatic mode.
 During retrograde, have manual control fuel handle pulled and
 be prepared to switch to manual AND fly-by-wire if the
 automatic mode also fails.

1. Manual control fuel handle 		- PULL DIRECT
2. RSCS switch 						- AUTO
3. ASCS switch 						- AS DESIRED
	Switch to normal, aux-damp, of fly-by-wire as
 desired.


ENVIRONMENT CONTROL SYSTEM EMERGENCY OPERATION

Cabin Pressurization
In the event the cabin becomes depressurized, it is only
 necessary to have the faceplate closed (automatic in Reentry).
 The cabin may be depressurized to eliminate smoke, fumes, or fire.
 The cabin can be depressurized at any time as long as the 
faceplate is closed.

In the event of cabin depressurization, cabin oxygen flow will
 automatically be shut off when cabin pressure drops to
 approximately 4.0 psia. The remaining oxygen can be lost
 overboard if the cabin is leaking and the cabin pressure remains
 above 4.0 psi. Therefore, depressurize the cabin if a leak is
 discovered or if oxygen consumption is excessive. If the cabin
 was depressurized by pulling the Decomp "T" handle, the 
cabin can be pressurized by pushing the handle IN and pulling
 Repress "T" handle. This will pressurize the cabin in 5 minutes
or less and consume O2 from the active bottle. When the cabin
 pressure reaches 5 psi, push Repress "T" handle IN.

Cabin Depressurization
1. Decomp "T" handle 			- PULL
2. Monitor cabin pressure

Cabin Repressurization
1. Decomp "T" handle 			- PUSH
2. Repress "T" handle 			- PULL
3. Monitor cabin pressure.
	At 5 psi cabin pressure, 
		Repress "T" handle 		- PUSH

Emergency Oxygen
In the event the suit pressure drops below 4.0, the
 emergency oxygen rate valve automatically opens and the
 suit circuit shutoff valve closes to prevent oxygen flow
 through the impurity removers, temperature control units,
 and the suit fans. The emergency oxygen rate valve may be
 opened at any time by actuating the Emer O2 lever on the right
 console. This action supplies oxygen for cooling and pressurizing
the suit as well as supplying oxygen for breathing. The 
"O2 Emer. Flow" light will illuminate whenever the emergency
 oxygen rate valve of suit circuit shutoff valve operates
 manually or automatically. During emergency rate operation,
 the oxygen supply duration is greatly reduced because oxygen
 is exhausted overboard.

1. To transfer to emergency oxygen:
	Emer O2 lever 					- EMER
2. To return to normal operation:
	a. Emer O2 lever 				- NORM
	b. Suit Fan switch 				- NORM


Alternate Suit Fan
If the No. 1 suit fan fails with the Suit Fan switch in the
 NORM position, the No. 2 fan will automatically cut in to
 provide suit ventilation. Either fan may also be selected by
 placing the Suit Fan switch in the No. 1 or No. 2 position.
 If the No. 1 fan fails, and the No. 2 fan does not cut in
 automatically, place the Suit Fan switch in the No. 1 position,
 and the suit Fan fuse in the No. 2 position. If No. 1 fan
operation is not regained, placing the Suit Fan switch in the
 No. 2 position will energize the No.2 Fan direct, circumventing
 the fuse switch. If it is impossible to regain suit fan operation,
 actuate the Emer O2 lever on the right console to provide
 ventilation.

If the No. 1 suit fan fails and No. 2 does not switch in
 automatically:
1. Suit Fan switch 						- NO. 1
2. Suit Fan fuse switch 				- NO. 2
3. If NO. 1 fan remains inoperative:
	Suit Fan switch 					- NO. 2
4. If NO. 2 fan is inoperative, 
	Emer O2 lever 						- EMER

		WARNING
Suit ventilation, either by fan or by emergency
 oxygen, 
must not be lost for more than 30 seconds
 or CO2 buildup 
in the helper will become dangerously
 high.


ELECTRICAL SYSTEM EMERGENCY OPERATION

Main Battery Failure
Failures on one or more main batteries may be detected by
 periodically checking voltage of each battery every
 30 seconds. If any battery shows less than 18 volts,
 turn that battery off.

1. If any battery is below 18 volts 
	Turn applicable battery			- OFF
2. If Main Bus voltage is below 18 volts:
	a. Check all bus and battery voltages
	b. Turn off all low priority equipment


Standby Battery Failure
The only indication of standby battery failure will be by
 periodic checks. If Standby battery failure is detected, turn
 that battery off. If the main batteries also fail, place the
 Audio Bus switch to EMER to permit the isolated battery to
 maintain communications. The isolated battery also supplies
 the isolated squib bus to assure sufficient power to fire all
 squibs as well as the retrograde rockets. The isolated battery
 may also be connected to the main bus through the Standby Battery
 switch if the Isolated Battery switch is placed in the
 STBY position.

If standby battery failure is detected:
1. Failed Battery switch 				- OFF
2. Check voltage of main and isolated batteries.
3. If main batteries are low, shut off all non-essential
 equipment.

If the main batteries also fail:
4. If radios are needed, 
	Audio Bus switch 					- EMER
5. If main bus power is needed:
	a. Isol Btry switch 					- STBY
	b. Stby Btry switch 				- ON

		WARNING
	The isolated battery should not be used to
	supply other busses unless absolutely necessary
	and then only for essential equipment since it
	supplies the alternate power source for firing
	retrograde rockets and the recovery system
	pyrotechnics.

Isolated Battery Failure
If the isolated battery fails, the isolated squib bus can be
 powered from the standby battery by placing the Isol Btry
 switch to STDBY. Immediate retrograde is not necessary
 unless the main batteries are also low.

1. Isol Btry switch 					- STBY
2. Check all battery voltages.
3. Before retrograde
	Isol Btry switch 				- STDBY


Complete Electrical Failure
Failure of the ammeter or the Ammeter switch can cause
 complete electrical failure by removing the ground for
 all capsule batteries. If all capsule power is suddenly
 lost, place the Ammeter switch to BYPASS to provide an
 alternate ground for the batteries.


Inverter Failure
If either main inverter fails with both AC Bus switches in the
 NORM position, the standby inverter will automatically supply
 power to the failed AC bus and illuminate the "STBY AC Auto"
 light. Determine which inverter failed by placing the 
ASCS AC Bus switch to STBY and monitoring the Standby AC Auto
 telelight. If the light goes out, the ASCS bus inverter has
 failed. Leave the ASCS AC Bus switch in STBY if ASCS inverter
 has failed; if not, return the switch to NORM, and place the
 Fans AC Bus switch in the STBY position. This provides
 for illumination of the Standby AC Auto telelight if the
 remaining inverter should fail.

When STBY AC Auto light illuminates and it is desired to
 determine which inverter has failed, observe the following
 procedure:
1. ASCS AC Bus switch 				- STBY
2. If STBY AC Auto telelight goes out, ASCS inverter has
 failed. Leave the ASCS AC Bus switch in the STBY
 position so that failure of the Fans AC Inverter
 may be detected by re-illumination of the 
STBY AC Auto light.
3. If STBY AC Auto telelight remains illuminated, Fans
 	inverter has failed. Place the ASCS AC Bus switch
 in NORM, and Fans AC Bus switch in STBY. STBY
 	AC Auto light should go out.


COMMUNICATIONS SYSTEM EMERGENCY OPERATION

If no voice or radio messages can be sent or received,
 one of the available communication systems may have 
failed.
1. Check position of capsule relative to ground station.
	Capsule may be out of range of all ground stations.
2. Check operations of UHF Hi and Hi freq, and HF systems.
3. Audio Bus switch - EMER will connect the Audio Bus
 	to the Isolated Battery

		WARNING
	Do not place the audio bus to EMER unless it is
	absolutely necessary because of the excessive drain
	on the isolated battery.


FIRE OR FUMES

Any fire inside the capsule will probably be an electrical fire.
 Therefore, attempt to determine the cause of the fire and turn
 off the affected equipment. The cabin can be depressurized
 to extinguish any fire and eliminate fumes.

1. If fire or fumes are severe, 
	Decomp "T" handle 				- PULL
2. Attempt to determine the source of fire or fumes
3. If source of fire or fumes can be determined, turn off
 affected equipment.
4. If affected equipment can be turned off, repressurize
 cabin.
5. Initiate retrograde as soon as convenient.

RETROGRADE

If the "Retro Seq" telelight fails to illuminate at retrograde
 time, the retrograde sequence can be started by depressing the
 Retro Seq button or the Fire Retro button. Depressing
 the Retro Seq button will start the normal retrograde
 sequence while depressing the Fire Retro button will fire the
 retrograde rockets. Use the Retro Att By-Pass switch to
 bypass correct retrograde during attitude failures.

FAILURE TO ATTAIN RETROGRADE ATTITUDE
1. Check attitude indicator and periscope to determine
 if capsule is in 
	retrograde attitude.
2. If capsule is in the retrograde attitude:
	a. Retro Att switch 				- BYPASS
	b. Fire Retro button 				- DEPRESS
3.If the capsule is not in the retrograde attitude:
	a. Manual fuel handle 				- PUSH RATE COMD
	b. RSCS switch 						- RATE COMD
	c. ASCS switch 						- FLY-BY-WIRE
	d. Use hand controller to position capsule in the
 retrograde 
		attitude.
	e. If attitude permission circuit is operating, the
 retrograde rockets 
	will fire 30 seconds after
 initiating retro sequence or as soon as 
	the
 capsule if in the retrograde attitude, if
 over 30 seconds.

RETROGRADE PACKAGFE FAILS TO JETTISON
The retrograde package is jettisoned 60 seconds after retro
 fire is initiated.
If it fails:
1. Jett Retro button 					- DEPRESS
2. If Retrograde package does not jettison:
	a. Retro Jett fuse switch 			- NO. 2
	b. Emer Retro Jett fuse switch 		- NO.2
3. Jett Retro button 					- DEPRESS


ASCS CANNOT MAINTAIN RE-ENTRY ATTITUDE
If ASCS does not reposition capsule to correct re-entry
 attitude when 
Attitude switch is set to RE-ENTRY:
1. Manual fuel handle 					- PUSH RATE COMD
2. RSCS switch 							- RATE COMD
3. Retract Scope switch 					- MAN
4. Use hand controller to position the capsule in the
 re-entry attitude.
5. RSCS switch 							- AUTO
6. Use periscope to see if ASCS will maintain re-entry
 attitude.
7. If ASCS will maintain re-entry attitude:
	Retract Scope switch 				- AUTO.
8. If ASCS will not maintain re-entry attitude:
	a. RSCS switch 						- RATE COMD
	b. As soon as the ".05g Switch" telelight illuminates
		Retract Scope switch 			- AUTO.
	c. Check that RSCS initiates 7 degree/sec slow roll.

LANDING

DROGUE CHUTE FAILURE
Drogue chute failure can be detected by the lack of opening
 shock and by a visual check through the window. Failure of
 the Emer Drogue Deploy fuse will fail the
 Drogue Override button.

1. Drogue button - DEPRESS
2. If drogue chute does not deploy:
	a. Emer Drogue Deploy fuse switch - NO. 2
	b. Drogue button - DEPRESS


MAIN CHUTE FAILURE
Main chute deployment failure can be detected by the lack of
 opening shock, a visual check through the periscope and
 window, and no decrease in rate of descent.

If the main chute does not deploy properly or is damaged:
1. Reserve deploy ring - PULL


LANDING BAG FAILS TO DEPLOY
1. Landing Bag switch - MAIN
2. Emer Land Bag fuse switch - NO. 2

