2.5 LRV CONFIGURATION FOR SCIENCE STOP 

a. 	Stop LRV and set hand controller in parking brake position;
	Neutral throttle. 
b. 	Perform LRV partial power down as follows: 
		DRIVE POWER Switches (4) - OFF.
		STEERING Switches (2) - OFF.
		± 15 VCC Switch - OFF. 
c. 	Report BEARING, DISTANCE. RANGE, HEADING, and
	BATTERY AMP-HOUR indications. 
d. 	Crewman in right seat release and stow seat belt and egress vehicle. 
e. 	Crewman in left seat release and stow seat belt and egress vehicle. 
f. 	Align HGA.
g. 	LCRU mode switch - FM/TV or TV RMT. 
h. 	Open LCRU thermal blanket per ground request. 


2.6 LRV CONFIGURATION PRIOR TO LEAVING SCIENCE STOP
a. 	Align LGA.
b. 	LCRU Mode Switch - PMI/WB. 
c. 	Board LRV left seat and fasten seatbelt. 

								CAUTION 
		Do not grasp the 16 MM Data Acquisition camera staff or low
		gain antenna staff during ingress. The handholds are designed
		for ingress by grasping the nandhold horizontal and vertical
		members below the payload staffs.

d. 	Verify hand controller in parking brake and neutral throttle
	position and reverse: inhibit switch is on (pushed down). 
e. 	Other crewman ingress LRV right seat and fasten seat belt.
 
								CAUTION 
		Do not grasp the 16 MM Data Acquisition camera staff or low
		gain antenna staff during ingress. The handholds are designed
		for ingress by grasping the handhold horizontal and vertical
		members below the payload staffs. 

f. 	Report Bearing, Distance, Range, Heading, and
	battery Amp-Hour indications.
g. 	Update Nav System to correct for drift, if required by MCC.
h. 	± 15 VDC Switch - PRIM. 
i. 	STEERING FORWARD Switch - BUS A. 
j. 	STEERING REAR Switch - BUS D. 

								CAUTION 
		The hand controller should be in park brake position and the
		drive enable switches must be set to an active PWM prior to
		setting any drive power switch to an energized bus. If the drive
		power switch is turned on and the corresponding drive enable
		switch is not selected to an active PWM, then full power will be
		applied to the corresponding drive motor when the hand
		controller is released from brake position. Should this condition
		occur the hand controller should be immediately returned to
		park brake position. 

k. 	DRIVE POWER LF Switch - BUS A. 
l. 	DRIVE POWER RF Switch - BUS A.
m. 	DRIVE POWEP. LR Switch - BUS D.
n. 	DRIVE POWER RR Switch - BUS D.
