APPROACH PHASE PROGRAM (P64)

			WARNING

		DES QTY warn lt will not be accompanies
		by MASTER ALARM; therefore, crewman must
		monitor MPS: FUEL & OXID QUANTITY ind.

	
1.	PROG ind - 64

2.	FL V06 N64
		R1 TR/LPD	XXBXX sec-deg
		R2 H rate	XXXX.X fps
		R3 H	XXXXX ft
	
	TR is estimated time remaining until end of redesignation 
	capability (change landing zone)

	LPD is the angle below LM body +Z axis (forward) and the 
	landing point.

	If not in AUTO, set LDG ANT tw - HOVER


3.	Monitor FDAI & observe LGC-controlled pitchover through
	forward window.

	LGC commands YAW rotation to bring designated landing site
	in line with landing point designator scale on CDR's for-
	ward window. Approximate look angle is in R1.

4.	P64 will switch to P66 automatically, or if you set PGNS to ATT HOLD,
	and DES RATE sw - +1 or -1




CUE CARD FOR P64:
