Simplified Rendezvous

Remarks:
This rendezvous method uses a simplified approach
where P30 (Externdal dV) is used to plan the prethrust
for CSI and TPI burns with input from Mission Control, 
instead of P32.
The burns are executed using P41 (RCS Burn).
	In reality, P32 and P3X is used to plan the burns 
with input from Mission Control, and P41 is used to 
execute the burns. P3Xs is still under development but 
has a similar approach. 
This method will soon be added to the simulator.

Use P20 to track the CSM, and the AGC P79 for the
CSM to track the LM.

Coelliptic Sequence Initiation (CSI)
	The CSI burn will circulate the orbit.

1.	To plan the burn with MCC, use the
	radio and REQUEST CSI.

2.	When MCC communicates the TIG and dV parameters:
	Checklist: MPS/P30 EXTERNAL dV

3.	When 2. is complete:
	Checklist: MPS/P41 - RCS THRUST


Terminal Phase Initiation (TPI)
	The simplified TPI burn will set you on a rendezvous
	trajectory with the CSM, using a hohmann transfer.

1.	To plan the burn with MCC, use the
	radio and REQUEST TPI.

2.	When MCC communicates the TIG and dV parameters:
	Checklist: MPS/P30 EXTERNAL dV

3.	When 2. is complete:
	Checklist: MPS/P41 - RCS THRUST


DOCKING
