DPS SUPERCRITICAL He VENTING (LUNAR SURFACE ONLY)

	DPS Propellant Tank Venting is
	prerequisite to this procedure 

1.	Vent supercritical helium:

PANEL 1:
		HELIUM MON sel - SUPERCRIT PRESS
		PRPLNT TEMP/PRESS MON sw - DES 1
PANEL 8:
		DES PROPUL:
			FUEL VENT sw - OPEN: tb - gray
			OXID VENT sw - OPEN: tb - gray
PANEL 1:
		DES He REG 1 sw - OPEN: tb - gray
		DES He REG 2 se - OPEN: tb - gray
PANEL 8:
		CB PROPUL: DES He REG/VENT - open

Remarks:
FUEL VENT latching valve is open when tb - gray
OXID VENT latching valve is open when tb - gray
REG 1 & 2 SOV's and vent velves will be left open to
insure that descent supercritical helium, fuel and
oxidizer tanks will be at minimum pressure when ascent
engine FITH occurs.
		
2.	Verify supercritical helium pressure decreasing
