2.2 POST DEPLOYMENT CHECKOUT AND DRIVE TO MESA

a. 	Verify hand controller in parking brake and neutral 
	throttle position and reverse inhibit switch is on (pushed down).
b. 	Verify switches and circuit breakers in pre-launch positions as
	follows: 
		NAV POWER Circuit Breaker - Open
		GYRO TORQUING Switch - OFF
		System RESET Switch - OFF
		AUX Circuit Breaker - Open
		BUS A, B, C, D, Circuit Breakers - Open
		± 15 DC PRIM and SEC Circuit Breakers - Open
		± 15 DC Switch - OFF
		MOTOR TEMP Switch - FORWARD
		BATTERY Switch - AMS
		PWR SELECT Switch - BOTH
		STEERING FORWARD and REAR Circuit Breakers - Open
		STEERING FORWARD and REAR Switches - OFF
		DRIVE POWER LF, RF, LP, RR Circuit Breakers - Open
		DRIVE POWER LF, RF, LR, RR Switches - OFF
		DRIVE ENABLE LF, PF, LR, RR Switches - OFF
c. 	Manually move the LRV away from the LM
d. 	Set parking brake.
e. 	Ingress left seat, fasten seat belt and initiate subsequent
	power up steps.

f. 	BUS A, BUS B, BUS C, BUS D Circuit Breakers - Close.
g. 	BATTERY Switch - VOLTS x 1/2.
h. 	Report BAT 1 and BAT 2 VOLTS indications.
i. 	BATTERY Switch - AMPS. 
j. 	Report BAT 1 and BAT 2 temp (°F) indications. 
k. 	Report BAT 1 and BAT 2 AMP-HR indications. 
l. 	Report BAT 1 and BAT 2 AMPS indications.

m. 	± 15 VDC PRIM and SEC Circuit Breakers - Close. 
n. 	STEERING FORWARD AND REAR Circuit Breakers - Close.
o. 	DRIVE POWER LF. RF, LP, RR Circuit Breakers - Close. 
p. 	DRIVE ENABLE LF and RF Switches - PWM 2.
q. 	DRIVE ENABLE LR and RR Switches - PWM 1.
r. 	± 15 VDC Switch - SEC.
s. 	STEERING FORWARD Switch - BUS C. 
t. 	STEERING REAR Switch - BUS B. 
u. 	DRIVE POWER LF Switch - BUS C. 
v. 	DRIVE POWER RF Switch - BUS C. 
w. 	DRIVE POWER LR Switch - BUS B. 
x. 	DRIVE POWER RR Switch - BUS B. 
y. 	Release parking brake.
z. 	Hand Controller reverse inhibit switch - UP position.

aa. 	Stop LRV and set parking brake. Reset reverse inhibit switch
	(push switch down). 
ab. 	Release parking brake and drive to MESA area for equipment
	loading. 
ac. 	Stop LRV and set hand controller in parking brake position;
	Neutral throttle.

ad. 	Perform LRV partial power down as follows: 
		DRIVE POWER Switches (4) - OFF.
		STEERING Switches (2) - OFF.
		± 15 VDC Switch - OFF. 
ae. 	Release and stow seat belt and egress vehicle.
