LANDING GEAR DEPLOY

1.
PANEL 11:	CB ED:
		LANDING GEAR FLAG - close
		LOGIC PWR A - open

2.
PANEL 8:	ED:
		MASTER ARM sw - ON
		LDG GEAR DEPLOY sw - FIRE; tb - gray

3.
PANEL 11:	CB ED: LOGIC PWR A - close

4.
PANEL 8:	ED:
		LDG GEAR DEPLOY sw - FIRE; tb - gray
		MASTER ARM sw - OFF

				CAUTION
			CB: ED LOGIC PWR A & B must be closed
			at completion of this task.

5. Observe +Z landing gear through forward windows

6. After separation from CMS, request CSM to confirm all landing gears deployed & locked.

7.
PANEL 11:	CB ED: LDG GEAR FLAG - open
PANEL 8:	ED: LDG GEAR DEPLOY tb - bp
