LANDING RADAR POWER-UP

1.	Select displays mode & verify landing radar temperature:

Panel 3:
	HTR CONT: TEMP MON sel - LDG RADAR
	Monitor HTR CONT: TEMP ind

Panel 11:
2.	CB PGNS: LDG RDR - close
3.	Monitor velocity transmitter power:

Panel 3:
	RADAR:
		TEST MON sel - VEL XMTR
		SIGNAL STRENGTH ind - >2.1 vdc

4.	Monitor altimeter transmitter power:
	RADAR:

		TEST MON sel - ALT XMTR
		SIGNAL STRENGTH ind - > 2.1 vdc
