2.4 PRE SORTIE CHECKOUT AND PREPARATION
 
a. 	Verify battery and SPU dust covers closed.
b. 	Verify hand controller in parking brake and neutral throttle
	position and reverse inhibit switch is on (pushed down).

								CAUTION 
		Do not grasp the 16 MM Data Acquisition camera staff or low
		gain antenna staff during ingress. The handholds are designed
		for ingress by grasping the handhold horizontal and vertical
		members below the payload staffs.

c. 	LRV driver ingress LRV left seat and fasten seat belt. 
d. 	Other crewman ingress LRV, and fasten seat belt.

								CAUTION 
		Do not grasp the 16 MM Data Acquisition camera staff or low
		gain antenna staff during ingress. The handholds are designed
		for ingress by grasping the handhold horizontal and vertical
		members below the payload staffs.

								NOTE: 
		If this is the first LRV sortie and this procedure sequence
		immediately follows initial payload loading (2.3) and LRV post
		deployment checkout (2.2), then at this point the C/D panel is in
		a power down configuration in accordance with step 2.2. ad.
		If this is the case then step 2.4 need only be a verification
		as it has been previously accomplished.

e. 	BUS A, BUS B, BUS C, BUS D CBs - Close.
f. 	NAV POWER CB - Close.

								CAUTION
		Do not torque nav gyro until nav power has been on for
		3 minutes.

g. 	Report: BAT 1 and BAT 2 AMPS.
h. 	BATTERY Switch - VOLT x 1/2.
i. 	Report BAT 1 and BAT 2 VOLTS.
j. 	Report BAT 1 and BAT 2 AMP-HR. Insure reading is stabilized,
	indicating the amp-hr  integrator has had adequate warmup time. 
k. 	BATTERY Switch - AMPS. 
l. 	DRIVE ENABLE LF and RF Switches - PWM 1.
m. 	DRIVE ENABLE LR and RR Switches - PVM 2.
n. 	± 15 VDC Switch - PRIM.
o. 	STEERING FORWARD Switch - BUS A. 
p. 	STEERING REAR Switch - BUS D.

								CAUTION
		The hand controller should be in park brake position and the
		drive enable switches must be set to an active PWM prior to
		setting any drive power switch to an energized bus. If the drive
		power switch is turned on and the corresponding drive enable
		switch is not selected to an active PWM, then full power will be
		applied to the corresponding drive motor when the hand
		controller is released from brake position. Should this condition
		occur the hand controller should be immediately returned to
		park brake position.

q. 	DRIVE POWER LF Switch - BUS A. 
r. 	DRIVE POWER RF Switch - BUS A.
s. 	DRIVE POWER LR Switch - BUS D. 
t. 	DRIVE POWER RR Switch - BUS D.

u. 	Drive LRV to level area. (+ 6° pitch) near the LM.
v. 	Deploy SUN SHADOW DEVICE (SSD). 
w. 	Deploy Vehicle Attitude Indicator to read roll.
X. 	Park down sun (within + 3° per SSD) and level (within + 6° roll)
	and set brake. 
y. 	Report sun shadow device readings and LRV pitch and roll angles. 
z. 	Fold (or reset) Sun Shadow Device (SSD). 
aa. 	Fold Vehicle Attitude indicator to drive position
	(pitch read position). 
ab. 	Pull system reset. Switch from detent move momentarily
	to reset position and return to off. 
ac. 	Verify BEARING, DISTANCE. RANGE Indicators - ZERO. 
ad. 	Receive calculated heading from MCC.

								CAUTION 
		Continuous torquing of nav gyro shall not exceed
		2 minutes of any 7 minute period.

ae. 	Pull GYRO TORQUING Switch from detent and operate to LEFT or
	RIGHT for proper heading indication, then OFF. 
af. 	Report battery 1 and 2 Amp-Hrs.
ag. 	Report battery and drive motor temperatures. 
ah. 	Report battery current while vehicle is in motion one time
	between stops.
